naijaecash.com 2012-05-09

# Privacy Policy | Nigerian Entrepreneur

### Privacy Policy

This website uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when visiting this site. These third parties may collect and use information (but not your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can visit **[Google’s Advertising and Privacy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)** page.

If you wish to opt out of Advertising companies tracking and tailoring advertisements to your surfing patterns you may do so at [**Network Advertising Initiative**](http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Google uses the Doubleclick DART cookie to serve ads across it’s Adsense network and you can get further information regarding the DART cookie at [Doubleclick](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) as well as opt out options at [Google’s Privacy Center](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

I respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at this site Nigerian Entrepreneur The following discloses how we gather and disseminate information for this Blog, Nigerian Entrepreneur.

 **RSS Feeds and Email Updates**

If a user wishes to subscribe to my NaijaEcash RSS Feeds or NaijaEcash Email Updates (powered by Google – Feedburner), we ask for contact information such as name and email address. This subscriptions provide easy tools for users of this blog to opt-out of these communications at any time. Your personal information will never be sold or given to a third party. We hate Spam as much as you do.

 **Log Files and Stats**

Like most blogging platforms we use log files, in this case Statcounter. Statcounter stores information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring, exit and visited pages, platform used, date/time stamp, track user’s movement in the whole, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. The data gathered are meant to help the webmaster optimize the website.

 **Cookies**

What is a cookie? A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. This blog doesn’t use cookies. However, some of our business partners use cookies on this site (for example – advertisers).We can’t access or control these cookies once the advertisers have set them.

 **Links**

This Blog contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We suggest our users should be aware of this when they leave this blog and advise that they read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Blog.

 **Advertisers**

We use outside ad companies to display ads on this blog. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the advertising companies and we do not have access to this information. We work with the following advertising companies: Google Adsense, Kontera etc.

 _ **Contact Information**_

If you have any questions or concerns please contact **_NajaEcash(at)gmail.com_** This privacy policy updated April 2009

Be Sociable, Share!

  *
